filebulk.com 2013-06-05

# Privacy Policy - FileBulk

This Privacy Policy and FileBulk.com's Terms and Condition, Abuse Policy, DMCA are collectively referred to as the "Agreement". 

FileBulk refers to the website FileBulk.com, its service and the company. 

This document is a binding integral part of the contract for our users. FileBulk may modify and edit the Agreement which will become effective immediately upon posting on the website. Your continued use of the website and any associated services indicates your acceptance of the Agreement. 

This Privacy Policy relates to our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of www.FileBulk.com (the "Site") This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through this Site. 

## PASSWORD

When a password is used to help protect your account and/or personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer be sure to log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from other users. You are solely responsible for the safeguarding of your password. 

## PERSONAL INFORMATION / DETAILS

In using the FileBulk.com service you may provide us with personal information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (based solely on the information you provided in your account). Personal Information that we collect may include your name, location, billing information (only if applicable and does not include credit card information), email address and postal addresses (if applicable). Personal Information may also include information you supply to us concerning your preferences and interests expressed in the course of use of our Site. 

For your safety and protection, your payment information is not stored on our servers. Our payment providers keep this information encrypted and secure on your behalf according to their applicable policies. 

FileBulk uses its best efforts in safeguarding information and uses reasonable measures designed to protect said information from unauthorized access. 

FileBulk is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of third-party websites and companies and shall not be held responsible for their actions. 

FileBulk is not responsible if you disclose personal information online that is accessible to the public. By submitting such information, you assume the risks and sole liability arising as a result of such information being displayed. 

## USAGE

FileBulk uses information related to IP addresses to measure usage, analyze trends and administer the website. We also use information we obtain by technical means for the above purposes and in order to monitor and analyze use of FileBulk and our services, for FileBulk's technical administration, to increase our Site's functionality, effectiveness, user-friendliness and to better service your needs and requests. 

FileBulk does not rent, sell or share your e-mail or information with third parties with the exception of third party companies we may contract to facilitate our services, including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management processing, etc. Content/Data uploaded to FileBulk is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. FileBulk may use cookies to store the preferences of users which may be rejected or deleted. They may be utilized to help improve user oriented services offered by FileBulk.com. 

## DISCLOSURE

When applicable and necessary, FileBulk cooperates with governments and law enforcement agencies/officials to enforce and complies with laws and regulations. FileBulk shall disclose any information to a government, law enforcement officials when we believe necessary or appropriate in response to claims and legal processes (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of FileBulk or a third party if applicable and to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider or can pose a risk to be illegal, inappropriate or legally actionable. 

## Contact Us

If any parts of this agreement is not clear to you, please feel free to [Contact us](http://support.filebulk.com/index.php?a=add).
